(Leonard:)...I checked in with you
to see how you'd feel about it.
(Sheldon:)Fine. The record shall so reflect.
(Sheldon:)Now, getting back
to the problem at hand...
(Sheldon:)...what to do with a washed-up
experimental physicist.
(Leonard:)I am not washed-up.
(Sheldon:)Oh, Leonard.
Lots of people Iove you
and want to help you...
(Sheldon:)...but they can't
until you admit the problem.
Ugh. Well, ladies, we killed the bottle.
- I had haIf a glass.
- I didn't have any.
(Penny:)Okay, don't judge me.
So, what do you wanna do?
Go to the movies, go dancing...
...lay down for a little bit? Ahem.
(Amy:)Or we play...
(Amy:)...Travel Twister.
(Bernadette:)Amy, really? Twister?
Excuse me, l've passed many
an enjoyable evening playing this game.
(Amy:)And I'm sure it's a lot more exciting
when you play with other people.
(Amy:)What do you say, bestie? We can do
shirts and skins. I'm shirts. Called it.